{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "  You ________ go to sleep earlier.",
            "a": "should to",
            "b": "should",
            "c": "should have",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "  She ________ speak English well.",
            "a": "cans",
            "b": "can to",
            "c": "can",
            "d": " ",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I ________ it at all.",
            "a": "can't to see",
            "b": "can't see",
            "c": "don't can see",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "  He ________ more slowly.",
            "a": "must to",
            "b": "can drives",
            "c": "should drive",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " She ________ a bigger breakfast.",
            "a": "shoulds eat",
            "b": "should eats",
            "c": "should eat",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " He ________ all day tomorrow.",
            "a": "must to study",
            "b": "must study",
            "c": "must studies",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " He ________ you with your homework.",
            "a": "can help",
            "b": "can helps",
            "c": "can to help.",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ________ her.",
            "a": "should to",
            "b": "should ask",
            "c": "should asking",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I ________ to the doctor yesterday.",
            "a": "had to gone",
            "b": "must had gone",
            "c": "had to go",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I am happy that I ________ wake up early on Sunday.",
            "a": "don't have to",
            "b": "have not to",
            "c": "must not",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}